[{"answer": "I was inside Macy's at the Lancolme counter which is close to the entrance of the mall area where the shooter was.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Where were you and what did you hear?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "No, they don't have training for shootings.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "I mean, do most people who work in shopping malls now in America have some kind of training for this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Well, I feel like that, you know, there is not enough consequences in the United States and, you know, unfortunately, it starts from the home and the home is destructing.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "What is your view about this ongoing debate in America which I'm vociferous about, many people don't want it all about gun control and about the ability of people like the shooter to get their hands on a weapon of this power and magnitude?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "I -- I mean, I saw the post that he was moving to Hawaii.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "What can you tell us about that?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "That -- I'm not aware of any of that.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Have you any idea where he may have stolen the gun?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Did he ever have any flare ups, any behavioral issues at all that would have suggested to you he could even be capable of this?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Not that I'm aware of.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Did he have any family issues that you were aware of?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "It absolutely is.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "It's completely baffling to you?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Yes, you know, all of our friends just are trying to comprehend what he may have gone through or what could have happened that led him to do such a drastic thing.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Is the whole community just in deep shock about this?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "LESHIRE: I mean, I have seen it on his Facebook.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Of his affiliation to guns at all?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "My response to that would be that would not be a good idea to have everyone in that theater or even a few people in that theater with a gun.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "What is your response to that particular argument?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, these aren't fully automatic weapons like you get in the military and many police departments have.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "I suppose my obvious question to you, Allan Gottlieb, is this, is why would anybody in America who is not in the military or the police force need to ever have one of these weapons?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "It only shoots one round --", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Well, James Holmes shot 17 people, didn't he?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "If you want to get a good solution you've got to look at both sides of the equation.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Can you stop talking?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "If you want to have a debate, you've got to look at both sides.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Hey, can you stop talking?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I don't think -- Piers, I don't think deranged people should be able to have a gun.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "-- that they should be allowed to continue to easily purchase or steal these weapons?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Because you're not telling the truth.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Why are you laughing?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "OTTLIEB: You should have the right to be -- you should have the right to be armed.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Who do you encourage to be armed?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what -- I'll tell you what makes alarm bells to me is that until 2004, following the ban on these assault weapons, then there was a ban on these AR-15s and now there isn't.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Doesn't that give you any alarm bell?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Do you have any idea?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "But to be honest with you --", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "How many?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I'm going to give you both sides.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Well, why don't you look at both sides?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Yes, OK.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "You do the same math that I'm doing?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "It should be easy for law-abiding people, for people who are mentally -- mentally deranged or people who commit violent crimes know it shouldn't be and we need to work on that.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Do you feel comfortable that that is easy to do in your country, Mr. Gottlieb?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "It is about this or a bomb or any weapon.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Explain to me why anyone in America should have one of these?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Of course not.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Are they evil children?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "People choke on hot dogs.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Then what do you do about this?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "They exist.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "That's why -- the question is why should anyone -- anyone have an assault weapon?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I think actually it does.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Do you believe -- does the Second Amendment allow you to have a tank?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "I think that that is not the debate.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Are you comfortable with everybody having a tank?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I think it is always something to be worried about.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Is it something genuinely to be worried about, do you think?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "Well, it's surprising.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "What is your reaction to this extraordinary proliferation in gun sales?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "Well, I personally believe that people have a right to protect themselves in their home, that they should be allowed to have a gun to protect them and their family.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "What is the answer?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Well, you initially said ever, and ever is a long time.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Do you think we'll ever see human beings on the Moon again, in your lifetime, in my lifetime?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "Well, I would.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "Would you like to do that?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "On my first space flight, we carried 18 mice on board for an experiment.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "It's a nice children's book Why did you decide to do this?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "She's doing very well, Piers.", "docId": "121212pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "How's she doing?", "qSentId": 673}]